2dollarwave.com 2018-11-11

# 2DollarWave 2x5 Super Matrix

**Your privacy is critically important to us. At 2DollarWave (hereafter referred to as 2DW) we have a few fundamental principles:**

1\. We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)  
2.We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
3.We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, 2DW collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 2DW’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how 2DW’s visitors use its website. From time to time, 2DW may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

2DW also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our testimonial page. 2DW only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to 2DW's websites choose to interact with 2DW in ways that require 2DW to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that 2DW gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register at our site to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with 2DW are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, 2DW collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with 2DW. 2DW does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

2DW may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, 2DW may monitor the most popular pages on our site. 2DW may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, 2DW does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

2DW discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 2DW's behalf or to provide services available at 2DW's webpages, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using 2DW's website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 2DW will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, 2DW discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when 2DW believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 2DW, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of our website and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with 2DW and our products/services. We primarily use our News Update page to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 2DW takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. 2DW visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 2DW's website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If 2DW, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that 2DW goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of 2DW may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by 2DW and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Comments

Comments and other content submitted to our anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, 2DW may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in 2DW's sole discretion. 2DW encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Please visit our sponsors below:
